{"data":[{"question":"___ is believing.","a":"Seeing","b":"To see","c":"Having seen","d":"See","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A gerund is a verbal that ends in -ing and functions as a noun \n\n","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The old man felt very sad with his son _________ in the war.","a":"being killed","b":"killing","c":"to be killed","d":"killed","answer":"4","explain":"\n-A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun\n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle\n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon\n-When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"We stopped ___ but there was no more sound.","a":"to hear","b":"to listen","c":"to listen to","d":"listening to","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Stop + V_ing: Don't continue doing something \n- Stop + To Verb: stop (doing) something to do something ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ from the space, the Great Wall looks like a dragon.","a":"Seeing","b":"Having seen","c":"To see","d":"Seen","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ with scubas, they dived into the water.","a":"Equipping","b":"Equipped","c":"To equip","d":"To be equipped","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+ When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the windows and the door, the workers left the meeting room.","a":"Closed","b":"Being closed","c":"To close","d":"Having closed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Past perfect tense \n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+ When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ that a storm was going to come, the climbers decided to put off their attempt on the highest peak.","a":"Having told","b":"Having been told","c":"Telling","d":"Told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Passive voice- past perfect tense \n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The old woman was taking a walk, ___ by her granddaughter.","a":"supported","b":"supporting","c":"having supported","d":"being supported","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participle phrase introduces a main clause, separate the two sentence components with a comma ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"The keeper was so careless that he went out ___ the door ___.","a":"leaving, unlocked","b":"to leave, locked","c":"leaving, unlocking","d":"having left, unlocked","answer":"1","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participle phrase concludes a main clause and is describing the word right in front of it, you need no punctuation to connect the two sentence parts ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"},{"question":"___ the message, her face went red.","a":"Reading","b":"When she read","c":"Read","d":"On reading","answer":"2","explain":"\n- The blank can be fulfilled with \" when she read\/reading\" \n+ When she read: stress the time her face went red \n+ Reading: stress reason her face went red","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"15","type":"1"}]}